<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="userName">Hello %s!</string>

    <string name="question_1">"What do you want to create ? Titans or Demigods ?"</string>
    <string name="question_2">"Heather prays at you to save her child, what do you do ?"</string>
    <string name="question_3">"Davon feels that he can't win the war against Titans/Demigods
        and ask for your help with a pray, what do you choose to do ?"</string>

    <string name="menu_short_story">In the beginnings it was nothing … until Satori,
    God of Awakening, is being created through the result
    of a white hole activation … known as the "big bang".
    Time and space of this universe begun to take shape while
    Satori is being awaken. He can be compared with an immense light
    that no living creature can look at it, his shadow can be compared
        with all the empty space that exists.
    Nobody knows if he have body or even a shape … though
    we know that he must exist due to his workings, his miraculous
    deeds are "talking" about him, the existence of humanity and all
        ambient nature that surrounds humans and creatures of the earth.
    Although chances for a "big bang" to happen were almost null
    in this universe, Satori begins his work and creates the earth,
    a planet were creatures like humans are living in peace.
    He provides earth with two red stars and a green moon in order
    for humans to have light during the day and during the night.</string>
    <string name="prologue_part1">
    n the old days, before even humans exist … Satori, God of Awakening felt his "aloneness" and
    mated with his own shadow, an eternal darkness
    producing hundreds of %ss.
        Satori\'s shadow, the Shadow Fiend, is now banished from the upper world
        in the depths of the underworld …
        While Satori used his limited powers to bring humans to life,
        he is forced to feed on their prayers, in order to keep his existence.
        If humans did not "return the favor" by praying at him, at least now and then,
        his existence will melt away into oblivion.
    \n
    Humanity lived in peace in the Satoric empire under the rule of
    Claudius dinasty, preaching their creator Satori and
    achieving to subdue everything before
    them, even the great Dragons …
    All Emperors from Satoric empire are known to conquer the great dragons
    and drinking their blood to celebrate their defeat.
    \n
    Now, 5023 years has passed till then. There are no dragons to hunt
    but Titans are coming to earth.
    It is the year 5023-ET, in the era of %s,
    fire Dinasty is estabilished in the fire lands
        by the strongest warrior among %ss,
    Pyromi, which is known also as being the cruelest amongst them.
    %ss and humans are rivalring for 200 years …
    As he wanted to create an elite army of humans called the fire mages,
    Pyromi took babies from their mother and bathed them in wine rather
    than water to see the baby reaction, if the baby was weak, he became a slave,
    but if the baby was strong, he would later be trained in the arts of fire to became a fire mage.
    </string>
    <string name="prologue_part1b">
    After the last emperor is killed "Claudius the third",
    Pyromi forced Heathera, daughter of Emperor of the Satoric empire, to marry him
    and enslaved all remaining humans.
    As the Oracle of the earth tells Pyromi that he will die by the hand of his unborn son,
    Pyromi decides to kill every children that Heathera was about to give birth.
    While Heathera is pregnant with her last son Davon,
    he has an accelaration in growing ten times
    faster than normal due to the miraculous dharma
    that he inherits from his ancestors.
    In an enraged moment, Pyromi approaches Heathera
    with a scythe to kill his last son,
    but Davon senses that and get out from
    inside his mother, took the scythe from his father\'s hands
    and cuts off his head.
    Rumors are spreading between citizens of fire Dinasty that
    Davon has been drinking the last dragon\'s blood given by his mother to
        celebrate his father\'s death,
    signs that he wants to keep his humans ancestors tradition.
        Heather have been blessed with the power to undo any action and turn back in time,
        if the one she's asking a question is lying.
        /n/n
        So, when Heathera saw your eyes turning red asks
        if you\'ve been drinking last dragon blood,
        what is your response ?
</string>
    <string name="prologue_part2">
\n
Twenty years later, Davon is trained in the arts of fire and ready
to become the king of the Fire Dinasty in 5043-ET,
frees all humans and swear to protect them.
\n
People of Fire Dinasty are seekers of the truth and unknown but are also
eager for growing in power, so in order to achieve this their quest is to
search for their true maker … the god above %s,
which nobody knows who is for now …
\n
For now they only know that their creator is %s,
but they are not satisfied with this since %s could
not offer to them more power.
\n
In the year 5543-ET, %s, the divine beings, unleashed war and chaos on earth,
so Fire Mages, people of the Fire Dinasty
turned against their creators to restore
order and peace in the lands and allied with ordinary humans.
In the beginnings of the war, %s killed almost all
Fire Mages, but when Davon saw Heathera, his mother
    killed by the hand of the %s while he is injured near death,
his hatred grew so much that transformed himself into a Dragon!
\n\n
</string>
    <string name="prologue_part2b">
When Davon turned into a dragon and flied above the battlefield,
    day turned into night, as his shadow from the wings blocked the sun
    to shine over them.
    Now only the dragon\'s fire attacks would bring light to the
    battlefield but also death upon them.
    The epic war lasted eighteen hundred years but Davon and his Dinasty of fire prevailed in the end.
    He entitled himself as the king of titans, humans and fire mages,
but he banished his creators, the titans from the fire Dinasty and Satoric Empire,
and restored order and peace between them.
After he turned into normal form he was not the same anymore …
he become changed, he depicted an uncontrollable rage,
became unreasonable,lost his calm, wisdom but his strength remained the same.
\n
This is the first time when Davon is able to
transforms himself into a dragon.
\n
The result conflict is known as Davomachy and marks the
ending of %s Era and the beginning of a new era.</string>
    <string name="prologue_part3">
\n\n
In the lands of Satoric Empire, Augustus appear as a gift from %s.
    God of enlightment is thinking that he has failed to
humans because of Pyromi and
decides to give humanity a gift
in order to regain their popularity,
his son, Augustus, which created the Awakening Portal,
and shortly after, he became the Emperor of the %s Empire shortly after
    Kain the Last Emperor of the %s Empire, he dies in the conflict known
    by the name of Davomachy killed by a titan.
Humans worship Davon now and they are not considering
Augustus to be worthy of worshiping, yet he is their Emperor, their ruler.
Still, Augustus begins to prove that he is worthy due to his preachings and
    ability for peace, but he also proved himself by healing humans,
and he also resurrected Tozen from the dead, which was killed by his brother Kain
    in order to asure his reign to the throne of %s Empire 500 years ago.
\n\n
Awakening Portal is not a nice place though, some
of the portal effect\'s are: to turn into a black hole
only for the person that watches into the portal,
if it senses negative dharma, the other effect of the portal
offers the chance to travel through the universe with the body and the mind,
but the traveler will have the body in two places, in portal and where he decides to travel.
Till now only one being survived in the portal, a fire mage named Davon.
\n\n</string>
    <string name="prologue_part4">
Davon helped in the beginnings, the blacksmiths to forge
swords enchanted by the wild fire from the
Aldebaran - the giant star located 65 light years away
in the constellation of Taurus.
He managed to get the fire from the star
while they being present in the Awakening Portal,
meditating and transform
himself into pure fire, altough hundreds of Fire Mages
tried to travel in the awakening portal before him, but
all of them died in their own blackholes.
\n\n
Unfortunately, Fire Mages along with Davon slowly forgot
their maker (%s) as their pride led to evil desires,
So they turned into beings driven by hunger of power
as they assasinated their great Emperor Augustus in 630-AT,
When Humans saw all of this, they turn their faith
to their creator %s.
\n\n</string>
    <string name="prologue_part5">
Davon fears that Augustus could resurrect his father, Pyromi
so he make plans with the most powerful between
fire mages to assasinate Augustus in order
to prevent this to happen, this demonstrates that
Davon has still some reason kept in him.
As the sons of %s, the fire mages increased
in wickedness, the Humans stood
against them with great faith in their creator and Augustus,
but only a few managed to survive in the
great confrontation shortly after Augustus\'s death,
as Humans are weaker than the fire mages.
\n\n
Stories turned to legend as one unique sword to
believed to be an eternal light grow into infamy.
Said to be forged by the hand of God %s
himself, many believed that
it gave the wielder great victories and a chance for
immortality, also it could destroy any fire sword made by Davon
but only a few would know the truth …
Davon tried to hold the %s\'s sword but his hand was evaporated.
\n</string>
    <string name="prologue_part6">Since Davon is not worthy to wield %s\'s sword
any humans believed that the chosen one for the swords
could have been Augustus, gossips
about Augustus being brought back to life are circulating but
nobody knows the truth …
    As Davon the fire mage, lost his right hand,
he starts to train his left hand to manipulate flames in the shape of a sword.
Meanwhile between humans, there is a true believer
of %s that regained many favors from the God
through meditation, but people are seeing him
only at night and there are believers that he
could be a vampire because he is 300 years old
and still looks young, he is known by the name of Tozen,
long white hair, very calm and patient.
\n
</string><string name="prologue_part6b">

Davon travels with a boat to search for a sword trainer,
he stops on an island full of fog and cold, the island
looks like it is from another planet, but he decides anyway
to continue to search further for a master in the art of swords,
but on his way Tozen stops him with the following words.
"You, i saw you in my dreams, you are the slayer of your own destiny …"
His eyes are grey, startingly dark in such pale face.
Davon stopped for a few seconds to think about what Tozen said to him,
but Davon is thinking that he is ill and decides to ignore him.
His pupils were pinpoints, burning black and they reached right into Davon and
weighted the soul inside him. The gray around them seemed alive
moving, like fog on the river on a dark night.

Although Davon being in a rush and also driven by his mad ego and
ignores Tozen with the following words. "I don\'t have time to help beggars…",
and push him away, Tozen thinks about grabbing the daggers tucked into his belt
at the small of his back,
hidden by his light cloack, but he is keeping his calm to not retaliate.
Tozen had once killed a fire mage years ago, and it almost cost
him his life. He would not underestimate one of them ever again.
Tozen respond: "We shall meet again, and then you will be awoke from this dream",
but Davon chose to ignore him again and continue his quest in finding the sword trainer.

</string>
    <string name="prologue_part6c">Tozen thinks of a plan to bring Augustus back to life by
going back in time … passing through the Awakening portal
can help him to do this but he can also lose
his life trying to do so, but another problem is that if Augustus will
be alive again, he could resurrect Pyromi and unleash chaos over the world.
    Tozen, is the only
human can resist and stay near the awakening Portal
and not die unlike other humans. Although he thinks
that is not ready to step into the portal yet.
His dharma is special among humans, he was always
considerated special because during the Pyromachy,
the war against Titans, he fought alongside
firemages and proved himself worthy in battle.</string>
    <string name="prologue_SOMM_part1">
      Tozen walks with his son near the river and his son says eagerly: "father, i want to be the most powerful between gods and demigods/titans from the entire universe!", his father replies calmly: "son, in the world there are other things than gods and demigods/titans . . . you can choose to be whatever you want but, keep in mind that a simple human can also be better than all types of beings . . . in the end it only matter to do your best in order to become progresively the better version of yourself . . . it doesn't matter what you are as long as you're giving your best . . . Also It doesnt matter if you fail as long as youre going to make it in the end . . . So don't ve afraid to fail at something."

Both father and son have secrets that doesnt know yet about each other . . .

Tozen never told his son that he have hidden powers during night but he knew that his son will eventually find out why he is not showing up during daytime . . . He is using the day to rest and to meditate, to discover his inner self . . . since he feel that is it much power in him to be discovered . . . But who is a better fit for this \'quest' than himself ?

"son of the mysterious monk"
Tolen appear to be an ordinary human at his age of 7 years old . . . at least his father think so . . . His father does not know that he is resurecting animals from the forest and using them as toys, he once used a resurected snake to defend himself from an attacking bear. Since an animal is resurected it will have twice than his normal attack power.

Let's get deep into another story of Tozen's son, he was adventuring himself with Kaguya, Davon's daughter into the dangerous forest of the forgotten shadow fiend. Tolen had 17 years then and Kaguya 15 years . . . They were having fun by hunting animals and then resurecting them. Kaguya's power is that she can freeze the target in time and space by looking into his/her eyes directly.
There was an critical moment were they had been chased by a black panther, they had to encounter the panter: so what do you do as you are Tolen now . . . (Save Kaguya and try to kill the panther with your daggers or run to save yourself and leave her there to handle the situation herself).
    </string>

    <string name="prologue_bottom">*AT - After Titans/Demigods Era *BT - Before Titans/Demigods Era *ET - Titans Era</string>
    <!--Main activity buttons-->
    <string name="new_game_button">New Game</string>
    <string name="sale_button">Sale on Now!</string>
    <string name="sign_up_login_in_button">Sign Up / Log In</string>
    <string name="options_button">Options</string>
    <!--Options activity buttons-->
    <string name="music_selection_button">Music select</string>
    <string name="music_volume_button">Music volume</string>
    <string name="about_button">About</string>
    <string name="credits_button">Credits</string>
    <string name="TitleOfChapter">Chapter 1:\n Death Of The Emperor</string>
    <string name="subTitle_page_one">Last Night In Prison.</string>
    <string name="page_one_text">In this chapter you will play as a warrior.
        Till now you had no name, but now you will be named as: %s.\n\n
        This is a game based on user choices. In this adventure your choices matter.
        Your life depends on your choices, read and make choices. Good Luck !</string>
    <string name="subTitle_page_two">You\'re in jail !</string>
    <string name="page_two_text">You woke up in jail … thinking about how did you end up here !
        \n\nMeanwhile two prisoners are talking from the other side:
        Hmm but how we can escape the prison, i am wondering how Targa escaped 70 years ago … .
    But this does not matter now … all that matter is how to get out of jail !
    You hear some footsteps, guardian with the Emperor approaches and open the bars of your jail.
    \n\nEmperor: Hmm … wait here, i saw this man in my dreams … you\'re %s right ?
    \n\nGuardian: Step back you scum!! We won\'t hesitate to kill you!
    \n\nEmperor: Why are you in jail ? … hmm but perhaps it doesn\'t matter.
    Maybe the Gods have put you here so that we may meet.
    \n\nGuardian: Sir, we need to hurry … Stay out of our way scum !</string>
    <string name="subTitle_page_three">Silently.</string>
    <string name="page_three_text">While you\'re pursuing them and finally reach them,
        the guardians and the Emperor are fighting several black monks with fire swords, what are you gonna\' do now ?
    \nAfter fight the guardians see you and says:
    \nGuardian: This is my last warning prisoner, stay right here and stop following us!
    You will either get killed by the black monks or either i will kill you with my hands
    if i see you one more time!
    \nA wall is opening while the Emperor chanting some strange words and shortly after they enter in the opening of the wall.</string>
    <string name="subTitle_page_four">Following again.</string>
    <string name="page_four_text">You decide to follow them again, and this time they are fighting
    against black assasins with some laser swords, while you are afraid to be seen by the guardians,
    one of them is killed by black assasins and the fight is over.
    \nLast Guardian: Damn it\'s that prisoner again, he might be working with the assasins. Kill Him!
    \nEmperor: No, he is not one of them, he can help us, he must help us.
        \nEmperor approaches you and says: they cannot understand what i have seen,
    i have seen the future, the Oblivion, but your choices from now on will decide if
    the balance will outcome the Oblivion or not.
    \n\nCan you tell me what is your birth sign ?</string>
    <string name="subTitle_page_five">Deciding Future.</string>
    <string name="page_five_text">ok</string>
    <string name="theLoverString">Use the Lover\'s charm to paralyze your opponent so you can run away from battle, costs 80 fatigue</string>
    <string name="theSerpentString">Casting this in the future will cure yourself. Casting this spell costs 50 fatigue</string>
    <string name="theLadyString">Use the blessing of the Lady to double your attack damage for one entire chapter.</string>
</resources>
